{
    "subject": "resource/Autopackage",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/C_(programming_language)",
    "human_readable": "Autopackage uses C (programming language).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8571068048477173,
            "question": "What programming language is Autopackage written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8388105630874634,
            "question": "What other programming languages could be used to develop Autopackage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649406790733337,
            "question": "Can Autopackage be used to develop software applications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7176658511161804,
            "question": "How does the choice of programming language affect the performance of Autopackage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5982151031494141,
            "question": "What are some common uses for the C programming language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5407329201698303,
            "question": "Are there any advantages to using C for developing Autopackage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5261701345443726,
            "question": "Are there any limitations of using C for developing Autopackage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2779058516025543,
            "question": "Is C a high-level or low-level programming language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22772441804409027,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a program written in C?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12785837054252625,
            "question": "What are some popular software development tools that work with C?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Autopackage uses C (programming language).",
            "html": "dbpedia_8583_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a program written in C?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8583_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is C a high-level or low-level programming language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8583_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any limitations of using C for developing Autopackage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8583_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8583_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\nResponse: {'output': 'no'}\n\nThe reason is that there is no mention of C programming language being used by Autopackage. The documents talk about Autopackage as a free computer package management system aimed at making it simple to create a package that can be installed on all Linux distributions, but do not specify the programming language used for its development or operation."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not contain any information about Autopackage using the C programming language. The documents discuss Autopackage as a package management system but do not mention its implementation details or the programming languages used in its development."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Autopackage does not specify the programming language used by the applications it packages. It focuses on creating binary packages for non-core Linux applications, irrespective of the programming language they were developed in.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on Autopackage's function as a package management system for Linux,  making no mention of its programming language implementation.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of C programming language in the provided context information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention any programming language used by Autopackage, and the focus is on its functionality for installing binary versions of applications. There is no indication that C is the programming language used to develop Autopackage.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}